{
    "subject": "resource/Shannon_RFC",
    "predicate": "property/president",
    "object": "Darragh Little",
    "human_readable": "The president of Shannon RFC is Darragh Little.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9250277876853943,
            "question": "Name the president of Shannon RFC."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8865468502044678,
            "question": "Who is the president of Shannon RFC?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8423062562942505,
            "question": "Does Shannon RFC have a president?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7677600979804993,
            "question": "What role does Darragh Little hold within Shannon RFC?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5941681265830994,
            "question": "Is Darragh Little involved in leadership?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5855643153190613,
            "question": "Is Darragh Little involved in sports?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.571749746799469,
            "question": "What organization is Darragh Little associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5301880836486816,
            "question": "Who leads Shannon RFC?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49734190106391907,
            "question": "What is the name of the organization that Darragh Little leads?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2749307155609131,
            "question": "What type of organization is Shannon RFC?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The president of Shannon RFC is Darragh Little.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4956_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the organization that Darragh Little leads?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4956_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who leads Shannon RFC?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4956_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What organization is Darragh Little associated with?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4956_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4956_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4956_102.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4956_107.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4956_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4956_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4956_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4956_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4956_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4956_90.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4956_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provided do not mention a person named Darragh Little as the president of Shannon RFC. On the other hand, they mention several people holding this position, including Mick McLoughlin (in file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_4956/re-ranker-msmarco/49.txt), Michael Moylett (in file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_4956/re-ranker-msmarco/55.txt), Stephan Hanrahan (in file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_4956/re-ranker-msmarco/30.txt and 46.txt), but not Darragh Little."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents do not mention any person named Darragh Little as the president of Shannon RFC. Instead, they discuss other individuals such as Mick McLoughlin and Michael Moylett in their respective capacities within the club."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}